If you've got something
to say, spit it out.
I never said it was taboo, and besides,
I don't like feeling like
you're tiptoeing around me.
I-It's nothing special.
But you said you'd "look into it,"
so why does it feel like getting
kicked out doesn't bother you at all?
D-Don't you feel the least bit sad?
I do.
I do!
And?
I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Loneliness and Girlfriend"
N-Nothing.
You chicken
Tch.
As if I could say,
"Sounds like you like me, then"!
Or, "So you're done
looking into it?"
Why don't you live together, then?
Y-Yaemori-san?!
Do you hear yourself?!
Well, if
you're
both
lonely...
It's right in front of your eyes.
Mizuhara-san's family home
should have a spare room or two.
You just said
you had no leads
on a place to live
And sharing a home is the idea
scenario for your "investigation."
You said so yourself
What is she blurting out?
How does Mizuhara look?
Differing
opinions...!!
She's red!
Is she blushing, or is it just the booze?
Are you telling me there's a chance?!
Water
That idea's so you, Mini-chan. Ridiculous.
That's putting the cart before the horse.
What kind of conclusion is living together
supposed to help me reach?
A boy and girl sharing one roof
is risky in so many ways.
It's the least logical thing we could do.
Trust her to be cool and rational.
Fair. Her feeling lonely is one thing,
and this is another thing entirely.
She doesn't miss me in that way.
You sure? I think it's the best scenario
to get to know each other better.
You're still stuck at that stage?
Don't turn this
into some in-game event
Heck, how about you two
just kiss once again?
That should tell you something.
Th-That was a last resort!
Yeah, Yaemori-san!
She did that to save my behind!
"That"
Don't get it twisted
Whose side are you on, Master?
Ridiculous. That's never happening!
I-It's never happening?
Really?
Please stop!
We've learned that Mizuhara
doesn't feel that way at all!
I don't think it's a bad idea to try.
Is the order of things
really that important?
Don't keep talking about this.
I'm more on Team Better Do Than Don't.
Nosebleed
imminent...
Don't rub salt into my wounds!
Gah! "Anything goes," my ass!
I never should've
asked her if
she felt sad!!
Let's put him down. Ready?
Wait, gimme a sec. Okay.
We should take him out before
he revives and attacks any civilians.
While he's still human
What is he, a zombie?
He might be having fun in his dreams.
He must've had a lot on his mind.
I'm not surprised,
after how he kept drinking.
You're partly to blame, too, girl
Did he say anything about me?
Anything else
Wouldn't you like to know?
smirk
I mean, I do feel bad
for saying I'd "look into it."
All I'm really doing is keeping him
waiting, knowing how he feels.
He said a buncha stuff.
He went "blah this, blah that" for, like,
two hours before you showed up.
But if I sum it all up, all he really
said was how much he loves you.
I'm sorry for making that
inappropriate suggestion back there.
This really only comes
down to how you feel.
Master will wait as long as you want,
be it three years or three billion.
Even as a zombie
I'm satisfied just knowing
that the label's changed.
Huh?
You went from "I don't know"
to "I miss having him around."
Lemme go grab a taxi.
You drank too much, dummy.
Kissing him again
should tell you something.
...love you.
I love you, Mizuhara...
Huh?
Wh-Whoa!
Keep it together, will you?
Mizuhara-san!
A taxi
One's coming over here.
Huh? What were you doing?
Oh, nothing. He was about to fall over.
Just holding him up
What an angel
You're so nice.
There it is. Over here!
You good to go, Mizuhara-san?
Yeah, I'm good.
One, two, and...
Man, he's heavy!
Was he this heavy a minute ago?!
C'mon, Master, help us out here!
I may have drunk a little too much myself.
I'll sit up front.
Oh, okay.
You're going to Ekoda, right?
That's right.
Huh?
Ekoda? Where in Ekoda?
Your place, where else?
Master looks like he's
at the end of his rope.
Not a moment
to waste
This a boat...?
What the heck? I will not allow it!
Oh, am I back in my apartment?
Wait, what? I don't remember a thing!
Did I do
something stupid again?!
I do recall drinking with Mizuhara,
but what happened after that?
Yes?
Oh, long time no see, Kazuya-kun.
Wha? Sayuri-san?
What're you doing here?
I stopped by on the way back
from visiting Chizuru.
I'm here to tell you something important.
Something
important?
Huh?
Well, I want you to stop seeing Chizuru.
What?!
Wh-Why?
It seems she finished
her... "investigation"?
And she realized she
doesn't like you one bit.
Wha... No...
Where's Chizuru-san? Let me talk to her!
The thing is,
KEEP OUT!
STAY AWAY!
she asked me to tell you that she doesn't
even want to see your face anymore.
I'm sorry, Kazuya-kun. I'll send you
year-end messages, at least.
N-No...
No way...
This can't be!
Wait, what?
A pillow... and a bed? Was that a dream?
What happened? I don't remember
what happened after that drinking sesh.
You're practically
replaying the same scene
Wait, I recognize this place.
Oh, are you finally up?
Good... day?
Mizuhara's place?!
Am I dreaming?
What? Quit sleep-talking
and wake up already.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Yaemori-san talked me into this.
It got really late last night,
and taking you home in that state
would only worry your family.
Are you listening?
Hey, what?
What the heck? I'm sick as hell!
I'm in this dream situation of
waking up in Mizuhara's place,
but I'm in no state to enjoy it!
Are you going to be okay?
You were a mess last night, you know.
It took all we both had
to get you here
You wouldn't budge an inch, and it felt
like you'd throw up any water we gave you.
Ugh, I made trouble for her yet again.
Always feels a lot older
the morning after drinking too much
What is wrong with me?
D-Don't you feel the least bit sad?
Now I'm just a nosy drunk
who got completely plastered!
Oh, is Master up?
She warned me about this once already,
He's still living his nightmare, though.
but I just did the same thing
again and had her look after me.
Not satisfied, eh?
I never
learn
I fail as a man.
The very image
of a failed man
The investigation concludes
with me getting an F!
No walking
this back
I want you to stop seeing Chizuru.
That dream was prophetic.
It's over! It's all over!
Just sit tight.
Go ahead. Get it all out of your system.
Yay.
I love you, Mizuhara...
Sheesh.
You must be Kazuya-kun, right?
I should die.
Nothing good will happen even if I live.
Mizuhara will reject me and
go off with some other guy.
I wouldn't be able to
bear seeing it happen.
Angel Sumi
This pessimism is the
acetaldehyde talking!
Getting that drunk was on me, too.
I brought this upon myself.
I'll never get a girl like that to
seriously consider me an option again.
Mizuhara...!!
Here, have some water.
I-I'm sorry.
I don't know how to face her!
This hangover might last into tomorrow.
I won't tell you not to drink,
but drinking that much
is just awful for you,
and it's not good to make
people worry about you.
S-Sorry.
It just keeps
piling up
Ugh, she is so done with me.
But wait, what's she doing here?
Hey.
Are you feeling good enough for a chat?
You can
stay there
H-Here it comes!
It's all over. She's going to announce
the end of her investigation.
Trust Mizuhara to try and do
things as promptly as possible!
Here and now
Mini-chan told me...
you can't find a place until next month,
and you feel awkward at home.
She knows about that, too?
I feel pathetic!
Is it all coming to an end now?
Our past, present, and future
are just going to get vaporized?
No! I don't wanna hear it!
I should leave.
Before she rejects me
I-I'll be fine!
I-I found capsule hotels
for 3,000 yen a night,
and I'm sure Kibe and Kuri will
let me stay a few days, at least.
And I have the
moving-out fee!
It's just a month. I'll manage somehow.
Don't worry about me. You can just...
You need to stay in bed and recover.
But I can't stay here two nights in a row.
Just one month.
Huh?
I'm only letting you use
this room and nothing else.
We'll have to share the bathroom,
but otherwise we'll maintain
separate spaces,
And laundry
stays separate
and you have to help clean the place.
Also...
You have to stay here, too, Yaemori-san.
She's here
And she got caught
Just the two of us would
be bad in so many ways.
This way, we'll just be roommates.
Nothing too uncommon.
M-Mizuhara...
You mean...!
H-H-Hold up! I can't ask you
to do that much for me!
Balance 180 yen
Usage fee 220 yen
Sorry. I found this
when we were in the taxi.
Ugh! My account statement!
From when I withdrew
money to drink
I know I'm partly to blame for this.
And you shouldn't waste the moving-out
money on hotels and other stuff.
But, well, you don't have
to if you don't want to.
I'll bring you some porridge
if you want some.
Okay with that, Mini-chan?
Uh, I'm fine with anything!
Huge help, actually
Master!
Wait, what? Master? Master?!
Yaemori-san.
Can you hit me real quick?
Ow!
Good! It wasn't a dream!
Gah! Nosebleed!
Sorry! I was aiming for your jaw!
Why an uppercut in the first place?!
Most people
would just slap!!
And that's how Mizuhara and my
limited-time, living-together life began.
Give me a break! I'm high
on adrenaline right now!
cackle cackle
For my first time
Rental Girlfriend
Wha?!
M-Mizuhara?!
On second thought, get out.
I-It's not what you think!
Yaemori-san did this!
Yeah! Don't worry, it's not vomit!
Wannanosaurussup!
We 60 centimeters high!
That was fun.
Kinoshita Kazuya
There's always tomorrow
Well, later
I want to see you again
I can, right?
Promise?
Smooch♥
Is it cuter when I face right?
Are you looking for
something in particular?
Can you believe that?
[Pre-summer new cosplay festival!] Streaming worldwide
Subscribe
Next time, the Heart-Racing
Living Together Arc begins!
Look forward to it, guys.
Show your support and
get that view count up.
Thank you.
A feast for the eyes.
Dinner's ready, Mother.
I'll be right there.
I think there's something
wrong with you, too.
How about you stop lying to yourself?
I think it can wait until after you've
come to terms with your own feelings.
Kitayama Kou
Kinoshita Kazuya
Keito
What a drag.
Are you okay?
Why do you have a nosebleed?!
Huh? I have no idea! What is this?
Secondhand nosebleed?
That's not a thing.
It's getting worse!
You idiot! Get a tissue!
It's not stopping!
Tissue!
Oh, man...
How is this going to end up?